[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[groaning] Mercy!
[yelping]
[groans and grunts]
[gasps. whimpers]
[grunting and groaning]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[screams]
[theme music playing]
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
[dramatic music playing]
[reporter] Make way. boys!
Comin' through!
Hey Commish. how about a picture?
We're still waitin' on the coroner.
but cause of death seems pretty obvious.
[tense music playing]
Who's the victim?
Small time second-story man working
his way up to cat burglar apparently.
Looks like he was in the middle of a job
when someone decided to stake his claim.
Well. did that thief take something
particularly valuable?
We're waiting on a list
from the museum director.
Not to imply that some crimes are
more important than others.
but it's a quarter to five in the morning.
Why am I out of bed. detective?
Because of this.
[dramatic music playing]
-[camera snaps]
-[laughs] That's the ticket. baby!
Front page all the way. [chuckling]
Damn it.
[Hattie. over TV]
I don't know about you. dear viewer.
some in Gotham call
the so-called “Batman” a hero.
But I ask you. does a hero commit murder?
Or sign his name in his victim's blood?
Mothers. has the Batman
made your children safer?
Or do his exploits inspire nightmares
that cause them to wake up screaming?
Who appointed this anonymous vigilante
judge. jury. and executioner
of Gotham's private citizens?
Who will his “justice” condemn next?
And where is the police department?
[Lucius] Bruce. Bruce?
Hello? Paging Mr. Wayne.
-Hm?
-Contracts?
Signatures? You're the one who pushed
all this into one meeting.
Of course. sorry. She just...
She's just doing her job.
keeping your eyes on her.
But it's just fluff.
Or does Commissioner Gordon have
an assassin in his little black book?
Also. the Batman is not an assassin.
You don't agree with her about him?
The guy saved my life once.
so no. I don't.
If there's one thing I know.
it's how to spot a friend.
The truth is. today.
I don't care about anything
that doesn't get
these contracts out the door.
Did your tax dollars
pay for Rupert Thorne.
and his poor. innocent little boy.
Matthew. to disappear?
No one's seen them since the trial.
Curiouser and curiouser.
Goodnight. Gotham. Sweet dreams.
[director] And cut. That's a wrap.
-Great show. Hattie.
-Someone bring me a drink!
-I said a drink!
-[groans]
[whimpering]
Ever since that pinko
took us off the gold standard.
the whole country's gone to pot!
One Manhattan. straight up.
I've owned the Batman beat for weeks!
How am I getting scooped
by the Gotham Gazette?
We're an evening program.
Can't beat the morning paper
when a story breaks overnight.
No excuses. I want solutions!
With the papers flogging the Batman.
the people will want feel good stories.
Give them that. and they'll flock to you.
The people are mindless sheep
who want what I tell them to want.
And what I want
is the Batman on my show!
Track him down. and get him in here!
What about Commissioner Gordon?
Put Gordon in the hot seat.
Force him to explain why his Keystone Kops
can't track down a man in a bat costume.
[satisfied chuckle] Not bad.
Make it happen!
Your wish is my command.
You bet your ass it is!
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screeching]
[music intensifies]
[dramatic music playing]
[Mad Monk] Last night.
I sent you on a retrieval mission.
Instead. you commit murder.
Explain yourselves!
We couldn't risk that burglar
taking the artifacts you sent us for!
Show me.
[man] We found them.
Just as you said we would.
-Plus more treasure for our lord.
-You have done well.
But these? Silverware and baubles?
These are not worthy of Barbatos!
It was the best there was.
I... see.
It is a sign.
Barbatos placed that man in your path
because he requires a new treasure.
He needs blood to fuel his rise!
You are certain? His time is near?
All the wealth you have given him.
all you own
and what the city has tithed...
When he rises.
it will be returned to you ten-fold!
While fire rains down from
his mighty wings upon the unbelievers.
you will be rewarded beyond
your wildest dreams!
Do not falter my children.
Only the worthy
will see his glorious rise!
All hail Barbatos!
[group chanting] All hail Barbatos!
[no audible dialogue]
Any progress on our cat burglar?
Multiple assailants. no traceable weapon.
Looks like the poor bastard got beat.
then stabbed.
Was that Hattie Tetch's producer?
My office. detective.
I'm gonna be a guest
on Hattie's Tea Party tomorrow night.
Sir. it'll be a hit job!
Who put you up to this? The mayor?
No. Ms. Landry approached me directly.
And I agreed it was a good idea.
For you to publicly defend the Batman?
Hattie can say what she likes
about the Batman.
Or me for that matter.
But I won't let her go after the GCPD.
If we're going to build this
into a department to be proud of.
officers on the street have to see
the top brass have their backs.
-Don't worry. I've survived worse.
-You're sure about that?
As you were. detective.
[dramatic music playing]
I'm sure Hattie would prefer
to have you on... if you want my slot.
Whoever drew a bat in that man's blood.
it wasn't me.
I know. Not your style.
Plus to my knowledge.
you don't kill people. Yet.
Even more to the point.
the coroner confirms our victim
was assaulted
by at least three different individuals.
You...
always work alone.
[sighs]
[dramatic music continues]
[man panting] Help! Help!
[grunting]
[panting continues]
[grunts. groans]
[whimpering]
[group chanting] All hail Barbatos!
-[chanting continues]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[yelps. groans]
Peace. avatar!
We seek your blood. not your death!
A final sacrifice to Barbatos.
It will bring his glorious rise.
so the worthy may--
[grunts]
[smoke hissing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[pained gasp]
[groans and grunts continue]
[gasps]
They say imitation
is the sincerest form of flattery.
I take it you will be confronting
these assailants
to make your feelings
on the matter clear.
I would be now
if I knew where to find them.
Hmm... When you say they vanished.
was that figuratively or literally?
These were humans. not ghosts.
Some kind of cult.
Or the occult.
If only we knew an expert
in such things...
[car engine running]
[jazz music playing]
[jazz music continues]
[both gasp]
Run along...
I have business to take care of.
I'll be there soon.
I assume you are here about the dead thief
and the bloody bat symbol.
What do you know about Barbatos?
-Barbatos?
-[guitar music playing]
[sighs] I need a drink.
Barbatos is a demon bat god.
who slumbers beneath Gotham City
until his followers sacrifice
sufficient treasure to summon him.
At which point he will rise.
destroy the unbelievers.
and reward his followers
with wealth beyond their wildest dreams.
How do I stop him?
You can't.
He doesn't exist.
Barbatos is an urban myth.
Pops up every few decades or so.
I was just attacked by cultists
who called me his avatar.
You thought a cult
devoted to an evil bat god
wasn't going to weave you
into their mythology? [chuckles]
That's adorable.
This isn't about you.
People like to believe in things.
God. government. capitalism.
Why not Barbatos?
It's so cliché. it'd be funny...
except...
What?
When treasure doesn't do the job.
the cult decides raising Barbatos
requires human sacrifice.
And these cultists
have already killed at least once.
Sounds like something their avatar
should put a stop to. Doesn't it?
Eh?
[dramatic music playing]
So. just before we go live--
Don't you dare touch him with your paints!
The Commissioner's rugged features
need no enhancement.
Good evening. Hattie.
You're in early tonight.
How are you. Commissioner?
Do you need water?
Juice? Something stronger?
Never touch the stuff
before an enemy engagement.
[facetious shock] Enemy?
Well. this is just
a friendly conversation.
It'll be fun!
Make yourself comfortable.
Dala will bring you to set
in two shakes of a lamb's tail. Ta!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Mad Monk]
The avatar's blood calls to its master.
Barbatos is pleased.
[weeping]
What is the matter. my child?
I've followed you for years.
Then tonight. I met the avatar and...
He's not even a believer!
Why would Barbatos choose him?
Hush.
-Have you shared this with the others?
-Not yet.
But my doubts grow.
We've all given so much.
Why does Barbatos not come?
[sighs] Your faith is that shaken.
[weeping] Forgive me.
Then meet our dark lord now.
-[neck snaps]
-[music intensifies]
[body thuds]
And may your sacrifice speed his path.
Any other questions
before your date with destiny?
Just the interview will be enough.
I think.
Good. Humor makes you seem
more approachable.
Just don't try to upstage Hattie.
-[chuckles] I'm sure that's not possible.
-[Hattie] What is this?
-Take your hands off me!
-[gasps]
-Unhand me!
-Stay back!
-[Hattie groaning]
-Police! Don't move!
-[struggling] Let me go!
-Drop the knife.
Good. Now very slowly--
[groans]
[body thuds]
[tense music playing]
Sorry. boss.
You're coming with us.
[dispatcher. over radio]
Attention all units. attention all units.
Kidnapping at Monoscope Pictures.
Commissioner Gordon
and Hattie Tetch are missing.
-[engine revs]
-[tires screech]
A suspect resembling the Batman
was spotted driving away from the scene.
All units be on the alert
for any sign of the Batman.
[Batman] While the police waste their time
looking for the Batman.
the cultists are gonna murder
Gordon and Tetch.
I have to find them.
Unfortunately. there's very little data.
Perhaps if we examine locations
of historic significance to the cult.
No. If this cult thinks I'm their avatar.
they're focused on the present.
not the past.
Midnite said they sacrifice treasure
to Barbatos.
The museum was their first murder.
Maybe it wasn't their first robbery.
I've taken the liberty of compiling data
on the city's recent unsolved crimes.
Perhaps there's a common link.
I'll investigate those locations.
Radio me if you find something.
[suspenseful music playing]
[struggling]
You all right?
Not my first scrap. Gordon.
[chuckles] East Gotham. born and raised.
[music intensifies]
Ungrateful tramp!
You're fired.
You've spent years treating me like dirt.
and I never knew why.
Until I met the monk.
He showed me my suffering
was all part of Barbatos' plan.
You suffer because you're a dirty--
What's this about? Ransom?
Hardly. Barbatos will provide
the worthy with everything they need.
You're going to kill us.
Blood of an ally. blood of an enemy.
You'll be the final sacrifices needed
to summon our lord.
[Batman] What do you have. Pennyworth?
[Pennyworth. over radio]
Based on my triangulations. I've deduced
the most likely lair for those zealots
is St. Bartholomew's Church.
-Good job. Pennyworth.
-[Pennyworth] Thank you. sir.
Godspeed.
-[engine revs]
-[dramatic music playing]
[group chanting] All hail Barbatos!
All hail Barbatos!
-[chanting continues]
-[unintelligible struggling]
Quiet. No one here cares
what you have to say.
Soon. she will be silent forever. my love.
[moans. kisses]
[dramatic music continues]
Would you care to do the honors?
[group chanting] All hail Barbatos!
All hail Barbatos!
All hail--
[collective gasp]
The avatar has fallen!
Strike him down. my children!
[suspenseful music playing]
[fighting grunts and groans]
Behind you!
[grunts and groans continue]
[struggles. gasps]
No one screws with Hattie Tetch
and gets away with it!
[effort grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[Mad Monk. echoing] Time for us
to go our separate ways. avatar.
My followers could've killed you
in the park.
I won't be so generous if we meet again.
Turn back now.
The only thing you will find
in these tunnels
is your death.
[dramatic music playing]
-[gun cocks]
-[Mad Monk] I warned you not to chase me.
Hands up. please.
I should thank you.
Convincing people to sacrifice
all their worldly goods to a bat cult
got a lot easier
when you came on the scene.
It was almost enough to make me believe
in Barbatos myself.
I never wanted to get you involved.
Directly.
Alas. cultists tend to get a bit zealous.
I take it as a compliment.
I figured you'd kill them easily
when I sent them to collect your blood.
-Why didn't you?
-I'm no killer.
Ah.
Well. unfortunately for you. I am.
[gun cocks]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[pained groan]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting] No!
[groaning]
[whimpering] You know. I have a pretty
sweet deal going with this bat cult.
I could cut you in.
[pained grunt]
[dramatic music playing]
Why am I not surprised?
Montoya. let headquarters know
we won't need to track down
the ringleader after all.
Where's my former producer?
I want to fire her again!
Blasphemer!
-[screams]
-[gasps. yelps]
[struggling. gurgling]
[gasping]
Have you come to show us the way. avatar?
Will you bring Barbatos' terrible glory?
No!
All hail Barbatos!
All hail Barbatos.
[crying]
Suffice to say.
last night was quite the adventure.
And I don't mind admitting I wouldn't
be here to tell you all the tale
if not for one man...
Commissioner James Gordon.
I can't take all the credit.
You held your own.
And of course
the Batman's arrival was key.
[laughs] The Batman inspired that lunatic
and his followers
to kidnap us in the first place!
[over TV] Sadly. the world is full
of weak-minded. passive people.
like my former producer.
who are easy prey
for charismatic charlatans.
-Not like you. dear viewer.
-[suspenseful music playing]
You're far too intelligent to fall
for someone like that.
Goodnight. Gotham.
Sweet dreams.
[music sting]
[credits music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm